<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LanguageData>

  <!-- Diamond -->

  <Diamond.label>diamond</Diamond.label>
  <Diamond.description>A extremely hard, clear gem. Because of its beauty and rarity, diamond is considered very luxurious.</Diamond.description>


  <!-- Amethyst -->

  <Amethyst.label>amethyst</Amethyst.label>
  <Amethyst.description>A hard, purple gem. Because of its beauty and rarity, amethyst is considered very luxurious.</Amethyst.description>


  <!-- Turquoise -->

  <Turquoise.label>turquoise</Turquoise.label>
  <Turquoise.description>A hard, blue-green stone. Because of its beauty and rarity, turquoise is considered very luxurious.</Turquoise.description>


  <!-- Sapphire -->

  <Sapphire.label>sapphire</Sapphire.label>
  <Sapphire.description>A hard, blue gem. Because of its beauty and rarity, sapphire is considered very luxurious.</Sapphire.description>


  <!-- Emerald -->

  <Emerald.label>emerald</Emerald.label>
  <Emerald.description>A hard, green gem. Because of its beauty and rarity, emerald is considered very luxurious.</Emerald.description>


  <!-- Lapis Lazuli -->

  <LapisLazuli.label>lapis lazuli</LapisLazuli.label>
  <LapisLazuli.description>A hard, dark blue stone. Because of its beauty and rarity, lapis lazuli is considered very luxurious.</LapisLazuli.description>


  <!-- Opal -->

  <Opal.label>opal</Opal.label>
  <Opal.description>A hard, multicolored stone. Because of its beauty and rarity, opal is considered very luxurious.</Opal.description>


  <!-- Ruby -->

  <Ruby.label>ruby</Ruby.label>
  <Ruby.description>A hard, red gem. Because of its beauty and rarity, ruby is considered very luxurious.</Ruby.description>


  <!-- Topaz -->

  <Topaz.label>topaz</Topaz.label>
  <Topaz.description>A hard, yellow gem. Because of its beauty and rarity, topaz is considered very luxurious.</Topaz.description>


  <!-- Quartz -->

  <Quartz.label>quartz</Quartz.label>
  <Quartz.description>A hard, pink-white gem. Because of its beauty and rarity, quartz is considered very luxurious.</Quartz.description>


  <!-- Peridot -->

  <Peridot.label>peridot</Peridot.label>
  <Peridot.description>A hard, light-green gem. Because of its beauty and rarity, peridot is considered very luxurious.</Peridot.description>


  <!-- Moonstone -->

  <Moonstone.label>moonstone</Moonstone.label>
  <Moonstone.description>A hard, milky-white gem. Because of its beauty and rarity, moonstone is considered very luxurious.</Moonstone.description>


</LanguageData>